MD. **ARAFAT** ISLAM

Jack of all trade, master of PHP. Fast Learner.

Summary

Full Stack web developer having 5 years of experience in PHP. Working as Laravel+VueJS developer for more than 2 years. Participated in NCPC 2016 and ICPC 2017. Completed 40+ full projects, 100+ bug fix & customization jobs. Worked with 100+ clients. Want to explore and learn new software technology.

Experience

Laravel+VueJS Developer – February 2018 to Present **Freelancer** (Local Clients)

- Develop full website in Laravel.
- Develop REST API in Laravel.
- Develop frontend in VueJS (SPA/PWA).
- SSR WebApp in NuxtJS.

PHP Developer – February 2015 to January 2018 Freelancer (Local Clients)

- Develop website in PHP.
- Develop REST API in PHP.

Wordpress Developer – May 2015 to Present Freelancer (Local Clients)

- Develop website in Wordpress.
- WP theme & plugin customization.

Admin, Mentor/Instructor, Problem Setter

- CSE Programming Club, PUST (2016 to 2020)

Education

B.Sc. (Engineering) in Computer Science and EngineeringPabna University of Science and Technology, Pabna
Jan 2015 – Feb 2020

HSC (Science) 2014 - 5.00

Major General Mahmudul Hasan Ideal College, Tangail

SSC (Science) 2012 - 5.00

Bindubashini Govt. Boys High School, Tangail

Portfolio

To check some of my recent works, please visit https://arafatkn.com



Contact

+880 1767764889
<u>arafatkn@gmail.com</u>
<u>www.arafatkn.com</u>
<u>github.com/arafatkn</u>
<u>linkedin.com/in/arafatkn</u>

Skills

- ✓ PHP/Laravel
- ✓ VueJS/NuxtJS
- ✓ Bootstrap, ¡Query
- ✓ MySQL, MongoDB, Redis
- ✓ Wordpress, Woocommerce
- ✓ OOP, SOLID, ACID
- ✓ Git, Nginx, Docker (Basic)
- ✓ Linux Server (Centos, Ubuntu)
- ✓ CentOS/Ubuntu Server, IIS
- ✓ Problem solving skills.

Awards

- ✓ Banglalink IT Incubator 3.0Winner (National Top 7)
- ✓ Student 2 Startup Chapter 2 Runner Up
- ✓ BASIS National ICT Award 2019

1st Runner Up